Pritam Behera (1) Featured

Software Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Solution Design, Solution Architecture, Continuous Integration, Requirement Gathering, Web Development, Performance Tuning, Java, Spring Boot, MySQL, Maven



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 8 Month(s)

Current Company: Integra Micro Software Services Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad, Chennai Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: java,mysql,maven,spring framework,spring boot,web services,rest,software development,software developer,application programming,solution architecture,continuous integration,requirement gathering,Web

Development, JSP

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Having around 3.8 years of IT industry experience in Software Development & SDLC Process.

Excellent knowledge in developing application using OOPs, Collection, MultiThreading, Exception Handling.

Experience in Enterprise world application and web enabled applications using Java, Servlet, Jsp. Spring(Core, I

Experience in Enterprise world application and web enabled applications using Java ,Servlet, Jsp ,Spring(Core, IOC, AOP, MVC).

Working knowledge on Design pattern like Singleton, Factory, Strategy.

Working experience on Software Designing ,integration and also good knowledge on architecture level.

Work Experience

Integra Micro Software Services as Software Engineer Sep 2019 to Till Date

Integr Micro Software Services pvt Itd as Software Engineer Sep 2019 to Feb 2020

I was working here last 5 month as Software Engineer .

here i was working one mobile shortcodes project.where i awered about json .

Gapbridge Software Services as Software Engineer

Apr 2019 to Jun 2019

Cartronics Technologies as Software Engineer Jan 2016 to Apr 2019

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Biju Patnaik University of Technology (BPUT) in 2014

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
JAVA	
JSP ,ORM, Web Services	
Spring(Core ,IOC,MVC,AOP)	
Spring Boot ,Hibernate	
XML,DTD,XSD,JAXP, JAXB	
WebLogic, Jboss	
Singleton, Factory, Strategy	
MySQL	
maven, svn	
STS, Eclipse	0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time